我认为可以把意图看作一个信封，
I like to think of intents as envelopes
里边包括了每一个人，或者说在这种情况下，你想把组件送到哪里。
each one includes who, or in this case, which component you want it
这还有少量的空间数据，
delivered to. And there's room for a small amount of data to be delivered,
把他打包为临时的。
packaged as extras.
原始的元祖将被提供给应用程序组件，
Primitive tuples that will be available to the application
最终得到并打开这个意图。所以你就会在信封上
component that ultimately receives and opens this intent. So an
看到一个清楚的意图，即被明确指定的容器名字。
explicit intent, explicitly specifies the name of the recipient, as
隐藏意图更有意思。
you can see on this envelope. Implicit intents are a
来，看这里，我们并不指定这个类的名称。
lot more interesting. Here, we don't specify the name of
我们甚至不知道他是什么。所以，
the class. We don't even know what it is. So,
我们应该如何显示出那个活动被推送了呢？好，
how do we indicate which activity to launch? Well, you
你也许知道这样的故事，你是否有时候听说用这些字母
know those stories you sometimes hear about letters with fake
作为假地址，但是依旧可以以某种方式找到收件人？
addresses like these that somehow still find their way to the intended
安卓系统的意图决议也是这样工作的。
recipient? Well the intent resolution system on Android, works the same way.
找到一个活动，让他能够执行一个你
Finding an activity, capable of performing an action
指定相关数据的动作。所以，并不是指定
you specify on the associated data. So, rather than
一个类名称，然后你表明一个你想要一个活动完成
specifying the name of a class, you indicate
的动作，还有
an action you'd like an activity to perform, and
执行动作的数据就可以的。
on what data that action should be performed.
像这样，我们想要解决一个活动，
Like this, where we want to address an activity
这个活动就是要具有浏览一个网站的能力。因为意图可以
that's capable of viewing a website. And because intents
跨越程序的界线，所以这个活动即使开始了，
can cross through application boundaries, the activity that started,
也很可能不是你的应用程序的一部分。所以，
may not be part of your app. So,
你可以像这样把功能包括起来，你可以
you can include functionality like this, browsing websites or
浏览网站或者打电话或者从你的地址薄里选择一个联系人。在你的应用程序
making phone calls or choosing a contact from your address book. All
里的所有东西，不需要你亲自去执行他。
from within your app, without you having to implement any of it yourself.
你甚至不需要知道这个
You don't even need to know about the app
最终服务你的请求的应用程序。你可以在安卓开发者的网站上找到
that will ultimately service your request. You can find
一些其他拥有与你相同意图页面的本地应用，
details of some of the intents supported by native
并从中了解一些意图的细节。
apps in Common Intents page of the Android developer site.